Correctional Association of New York; Records apap014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Records received in, 2006 August; 11
  - Annual Reports 1921-1922 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 25)
  - Annual Reports 1924-1929, vol. 25 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 26)
  - Annual Reports 1925-1927 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 27)
  - Annual Reports 1928-1929 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 28)
  - Annual Reports 1930-1931 Prison Association of New York (volume number is not marked) (Inventory 29)
  - Annual Reports 1930-1931, vol. 26 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 30)
  - Annual Reports 1932-1933, vol. 27 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 31)
  - Annual Reports 1932-1934 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 32)
  - Annual Reports 1934-1935 vol. 28 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 33)
  - Annual Reports 1935-1936 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 34)
  - Annual Reports 1936-1938, vol. 29 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 35)
  - Annual Reports 1937-1939 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 36)
  - Annual Reports 1939-1940, vol. 30 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 37)
  - Annual Reports 1940-1941 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 38)
  - Annual Reports 1941-1942 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 39)
  - Annual Reports 1942-1943 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 40)
  - Annual Reports 1943-1944 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 41)
  - Annual Reports 1944-1945 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 42)
  - Annual Reports 1945-1946 Prison Association of New York 1945-1946 (Inventory 43)
  - Annual Reports 1947-1948 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 44)
  - Annual Reports 1947-1948 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 45)
  - Annual Reports 1949-1950 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 46)
  - Annual Reports 1949-1951 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 47)
  - Annual Reports 1951-1952 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 48)
  - Annual Reports 1952-1954 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 49)
  - Annual Reports 1953-1954 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 50)
  - Annual Reports 1955-1956 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 51)
  - Annual Reports 1957-1959 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 52)
  - Annual Reports 1957-1959 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 53)
  - Annual Reports 1960-1961 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 54)
  - Annual Reports 1960-1961 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 55)
  - Annual Reports 1962-1964 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 56)
  - Annual Reports 1965-1969 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 57)
  - Anti-crime Strategies at a Time of Fiscal Constraint, 1990 (Inventory 58)
  - Assignment of Mortgage Miller, King, Lane & Trafford, Attorneys, 1916 (Inventory 59)
  - Attica 1982: An Analysis of Current Conditions in New York State Prisons (Inventory 60)
  - Blueprints Kenneth Ricci, Architect, 1970 (Inventory 61)
  - Blueprints Simon Thoresen & Associates, Architects, plans to turn basement into offices, 1983 (Inventory 62)
  - Bond -- The Prison Association of New York to The Corporation of the Brick Presbeyterian Church Eugene Smith, Attorney, loan papers for building, 1903 (Inventory 63)
  - CA Brochure (blue, old), 2001 (Inventory 64)
  - CA Brochure (green), Undated (Inventory 65)
  - CA Newsletter, 2003 Fall (Inventory 66)
  - CA Newsletter, 2000 July (Inventory 67)
  - CA Newsletter, 2003 Spring (Inventory 68)
  - CA Newsletter, 2001 Summer (Inventory 69)
  - CA Newsletter, 2002 Summer (Inventory 70)
  - CA Newsletter, 2004 Summer (Inventory 71)
  - CA Newsletter, 2002 Winter (Inventory 72)
  - CD with CA website files, 2001 (Inventory 73)
  - CA/Osborne Annual Report 1991-92, 1992 (Inventory 74)
  - CA/Osborne Newsletter, 1998 April (Inventory 75)
  - CA/Osborne Newsletter, 1998 July (Inventory 76)
  - CA/Osborne Newsletter, 1999 July (Inventory 77)
  - CA/Osborne Newsletter, 1995 May (Inventory 78)
  - Certificate of name change and other documents including CA administration typewritten documents and copies folder containing certificate of name change and pertaining documents, 1961; Undated (Inventory 79)
  - Children's Lobby Day publications booklet with drawings and letters of children of incarcerated mothers, talking about the Rockefeller Drug Laws, 2001 (Inventory 80)
  - Coalition for Women Prisoners button: says Coalition Demands Justice for Women Prisoners, Undated (Inventory 81)
  - Contract -- Cornelius B. Gold and Prison Association of New York Eugene Smith, Attorney, 1887 (Inventory 82)
  - Do They Belong in Prison? The Impact of New York's Mandatory Sentencing Laws on the Administration of Justice, 1985 (Inventory 83)
  - Doing Idle Time: An Investigation of Inmate Idleness in New York's Prisons and Recommendations for Change, 1984 (Inventory 84)
  - Drop the Rock Button (red and black) says: Drob the Rock -- Repeal the Rockefeller Drug Laws Tuesday, March 27, 2001 Albany, NY (Inventory 85)
  - Employment and Incarceration in New York CA and Robert J. Milano Graduate School of Management and Urban Policy, 1996 (Inventory 86)
  - Executive Committee Meeting Minutes 1867-1878 Prison Association of New York (Inventory 87)
  - Imprisoned Generation: Young Men under Criminal Justice Custody in New York State, 1990 (Inventory 88)
  - Justice 4 Youth Coalition brochure, 2002 (Inventory 89)
  - New York City Jail Crisis: Causes, Costs, and Solutions Diane Steelman, 1984 (Inventory 90)
  - Proofs from old newsletters, Undated (Inventory 91)
  - Proposed Occupancy drawings Paul Segal Associates, Architects, 1990 (Inventory 92)
  - Rethinking Juvenile Justice in New York City, 2002 (Inventory 93)
  - Rikers Review, 2001 Summer (Inventory 94)
  - State of New York No. 243 / Fourth Annual Report of the New York Prison Association Prison Association of New York, 1849 (Inventory 95)
  - Stupid, Irrational and Barbarous: New York Judges Speak against the Rockefeller Drug Laws, 2001 (Inventory 96)
  - The Mentally Ill in New York's Prisons: Problems and Solutions, 1987 (Inventory 97)
  - The State of the Prisons in England and Wales by John Howard, 1777 (Inventory 99)
    Includes pages 1-272. missing about 200 pages and back cover.
  - Toward a Crime Prevention Strategy: Using Savings from Jail Budget to Support Anti-crime Programs Diane Steelman, 1985 (Inventory 100)